{
    "id": "c42bccf6755847a49b9971b47227a33e",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Flour is made …………………………. wheat.",
            "description": "Make from is used when a material changes into a completely different form.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8c116eb45e4e4b0885eccf4c2111d036"
        },
        {
            "question": "He got little ………………………….. for his work.",
            "description": "An award is a prize. A reward is an acknowledgement. ",
            "answers": [
                "award",
                "reward"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff8a170a84e44b15a8b3ad8ad9330217"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was deeply ………………………….. by their kindness.",
            "description": "Effect is a noun affect is the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "effected",
                "affected"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9fb1d865648b47b69cebb049ced061a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "This theory has several ……………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "implications",
                "applications"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11aeafc012364a54b59f3770ce87cfbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I could not understand the …………………………. of his statement.",
            "description": "Implication is the conclusion that can be drawn from something.",
            "answers": [
                "applications",
                "implications"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79471be89a87456da20784aba891d544"
        },
        {
            "question": "People ………………………… when they cannot find enough job opportunities in their native place.",
            "description": "To emigrate is to leave your home country. To immigrate is to arrive in a new country.",
            "answers": [
                "immigrate",
                "emigrate"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f93d6e018d4d4fffa7ada1e9295b3822"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. face many problems in their adopted country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Emigrants",
                "Immigrants"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aa66305c62bf448dbb7c02937c937ece"
        },
        {
            "question": "You never …………………………… to amaze me.",
            "description": "Cease means stop.",
            "answers": [
                "seize",
                "cease",
                "ceace"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "863c82b72ced468389d56385926099ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kerala is on the west ………………………… of India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "coast",
                "cost"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "805ad8bdbe5b467b975f032d1a6641fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………….. to working hard.",
            "description": "Accustomed to means used to.",
            "answers": [
                "accused",
                "accustomed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "73ca7e32f70d430188b9359f3f3ae3ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Metals …………………………….. on heating.",
            "description": "Expend means spend.",
            "answers": [
                "expand",
                "expend"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a8090709d1843f998b20dd2973d21bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are still …………………………… the demise of their leader.",
            "description": "Mourning is the expression of sorrow for someone's death.",
            "answers": [
                "moaning",
                "mourning",
                "morning"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "943c6f89f0084ca4a505f7b653279a7e"
        }
    ]
}